Initiating the "sol_launch.py" launch file for three robots and outputting to both stdout and the results.log file.
The command initializes the environment with three robots and opens RViz for visualization.
Currently, the robots are in the exploration phase, strategizing their approach to navigate while building an understanding of the environment in terms of costmaps.
Each robot is now estimating the locations of items relative to the map, approaching towards these items while avoiding static obstacles.
With Robots 2 and 3 in close proximity, and Robot 3 carrying a higher-value item, a central node commands Robot 1 to stop.
Robot 2 proceeds, maintaining movement within a safe distance.
Robot 3 heads back, using the costmap to navigate a path to home that avoids any items.
It carefully avoids picking up any items, prioritizing higher value retrieval.
Robot 2 enters a constraint state as it is too close to an obstacle for safe rotation without risking collision.
Robot 2's path is carefully planned to avoid obstacles, items, and Robot 3, utilizing shared location data.
Robot 1, nearing the home zone, is transporting a green ball.
The robots approach their starting points, guided by the NAV2 stack and sensor data.
Data logging in progress allows for real-time analysis of the system's performance.
The robots prepare for another exploration phase. As they are influenced by inherent randomness rather than determinism, the goes towards different item this time.
Robot 1 is going to swaps a green ball for one of higher value. Robot 2 was paused as Robot 1 approaches an item in close proximity.
Robot 1 now targets the blue balls, aiming to collect the nearest one.
Robot 2, upon finding a green ball, carefully maneuvers to collect it while avoiding obstacles by curving the path.
After collection, robot 1 smartly planned a path that avoids the cluser of items.
Discovering a higher-priority blue ball, Robot 2 adjusts its objective and proceeds to collect it.
Robot 1 has planned the path to avoid the item but would not be able to as while doing so it risk the chance of collision by spin, thus the state manager will make sure this won't happen.
Metrics from the simulation are dynamically updated and displayed.
Metrics are visualized directly using a Python Notebook for detailed analysis.
Graphs and heatmaps encapsulate the entire simulation and highlighting robot movements across the map.